haha
today is the sixty-sixth
I don't want to take that risk anymore
to set up a workshop
put chair
all over again and talk
caramba
now i will set the date
will give good
and then I order snack
and then we create a super high orbit
in our dreams
is on
I need to do this
reach more people
you can't keep thinking
only in this local guys know
because if I take Pau,
that's it
but if you want to know something
is that the indicative of no is the path of yes
put the music there
My love is over
And i'll never let you GO
i can't give up my workshop
because one only went wrong
is on
change the strategy
and we go after winning this war
Thursday at eight o'clock
no pear it's half past eight
Thursday at half past eight in the morning
I will do the workshop
online beatbox
that's it brother
let's go upstairs bro
tamo together
until tomorrow